http://www.bibsoc.org.uk/content/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
The Bibliographical Society (the Society) collects and holds the following personal details for each of its members:
Full name
Mailing address
Email address
Accordingly, no special categories of personal data, such as ‘Sensitive Personal Data’, is collected or processed. The Society collects and stores these data specifically and solely for the purposes of fulfilling its obligations to its members, namely to distribute copies of The Library, provide electronic access to The Library, maintain a list of current members, and to provide regular updates about the scholastic activities of the Society.
The Society shares these data with the digital publisher of The Library (Oxford University Press), and the distributor of the print edition (D & M Heritage), for the sole purpose of providing access to The Library in its digital and printed forms.
Industry-standard security measures are employed to protect these data and to ensure that access to these data is limited only to those who will use it for its intended purpose.
Personal data is not transferred outside of the EU.
Latest news
Recordings of lectures
Posted:
05 December 2020
The Bibliographical...
Virtual edition of The Library on Venetian printing
Posted:
05 December 2020
...
Council's Choice for December
Posted:
02 December 2020
...
Euclid in print, 1482–1703
Posted:
24 November 2020
...
Council's choice for November
Posted:
24 November 2020
A monthly series of bibliography- or book-related...
Sitemap
About UsOfficers and CouncilCommitteesCouncil's choiceGold MedallistsPast PresidentsGovernanceLibrary and ArchivesLibraries at Risk PolicyContact UsOther Bibliographical SocietiesLegacy Gifts to the SocietyPrivacy PolicyPublicationsNew PublicationRecent PublicationsCurrent PublicationsOrdersPast PublicationsAdditions and correctionse-PublicationsWork in progressPublications PolicyThe LibraryAdvertisingEditorsNotes for ContributorsEditorial BoardMembers' Online AccessNon-Members' SubscriptionsVirtual issues of The LibraryFellowships and BursariesKatharine F Pantzer Jr Research FellowshipMajor GrantsMinor GrantsConference SubventionsAd-hoc funding requestsGuidelines for ApplicationsApplication ProcedureGrants AwardedMembershipSubscriptionsBenefitsMembership EnquiriesNewsCurrent NewsNews ArchiveEventsUpcoming EventsLecture ProgrammeRecordings of lectures
Made by Adaptive
Powered by Drupal
This site uses cookies
User login
